{
    "id": "7cc0a708753c46dba0f29a13fdafe282",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………………….. he comes in time, we will not be able to meet him.",
            "description": "Unless expresses a condition. It is similar to if not.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Without",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "08360083be644938ba7198a626215a49"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. on tip-toe, he reached for the mango.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Standing",
                "Stood"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "35f5851653124c0cb98285fe035e16b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sam, ………………………… was my student many years ago, is now an accomplished cardiologist.",
            "description": "In non-identifying relatives clauses, that cannot be used. ",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "627238cbdb774409b56d93eae0abf6b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… a noise, the cat ran away.",
            "description": "The cat heard a noise. The cat ran away. We can combine these two with a present participle. ",
            "answers": [
                "Hearing",
                "Heard",
                "Hear"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1d74f74992e049acb4ee3c784dd5bba4"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. hard you work, you will not be able to finish this job.",
            "description": "However means it doesn't matter how.",
            "answers": [
                "However",
                "How ever",
                "How"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e2e8b17320a34a678cabfecceea69475"
        },
        {
            "question": "The faster you run, ………………………… you get tired.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the soon",
                "the sooner",
                "sooner"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "25c434cefe114da5a806004ff318f2a7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The mangoes ………………………. I bought yesterday were sour.",
            "description": "In identifying relative clauses, both which and that can refer to things.",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "97fd944ca1404a7398d9921d90037ffa"
        },
        {
            "question": "If he had listened to my advice, he ……………………………. in trouble.",
            "description": "In the third conditional, we use a past perfect tense in the if-clause and would have + past participle in the main clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "will not land",
                "would not land",
                "would not have landed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "45fa685ca7ff4523aa0a690a0ee43f33"
        },
        {
            "question": "The more you study, ………………………….. you remember.",
            "description": "In both clauses we use the + comparative. ",
            "answers": [
                "the less",
                "the lesser",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3484d1ba7c644626a6833ad47b7c8676"
        },
        {
            "question": "Uma with ………………………… I went to Beijing is a rich girl.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d734f3589f2049f4891cdc167e073d4e"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… their best efforts, they could not save her.",
            "description": "Despite is a preposition. It is followed by a noun/noun phrase. ",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "However",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e5610ce5e06847aeae46099e39ea1b6f"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. you are honest, I will trust you.",
            "description": "Since gives the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "So",
                "Hence"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0d47c42da5f744b2a7914c22e9ded04d"
        }
    ]
}